<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rules on Lorecraft</title><link>https://www.lorecraft.cc/categories/rules/</link><description>Recent content in rules on Lorecraft</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Aaron Thompson</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.lorecraft.cc/categories/rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Base Rules</title><link>https://www.lorecraft.cc/rules/base-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lorecraft.cc/rules/base-rules/</guid><description>There are 6 server rules that will pertain to every interaction with the server. They are:
No Griefing: Griefing is defined as breaking, placing, or otherwise modifying blocks on another player&amp;rsquo;s private property without their permission. No Stealing: Stealing is defined as taking or destroying another player&amp;rsquo;s private property (items, mobs, etc.) without their permission No Killing: Except during PvP situations. All PvPers involved must agree to the fight beforehand for it to be considered a PvP situation.</description></item><item><title>Current SWAG Resolutions</title><link>https://www.lorecraft.cc/rules/swag-in-effect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lorecraft.cc/rules/swag-in-effect/</guid><description>Below is a list of the current SWAG rules that are in effect:
Resolution # Date Passed Resolution 1 November 23, 2022 Change the gamerule playersSleepingPercent to 25 instead of 50</description></item><item><title>Plugins Utilized</title><link>https://www.lorecraft.cc/rules/plugins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lorecraft.cc/rules/plugins/</guid><description>In this server, there are a couple important plugins that the server utilizes in order to elevate the vanilla surivival experience. Below is a list of the plugins, a quick reference on how to use them, and a link to more documentation.
Geyser Dynmap Skoice Geyser Geyser self describes itself on their website here as follows:
Geyser is a proxy, bridging the gap between Minecraft: Bedrock Edition and Minecraft: Java Edition servers.</description></item><item><title>SWAG Utilization</title><link>https://www.lorecraft.cc/rules/swag-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.lorecraft.cc/rules/swag-guidelines/</guid><description>Layout of SWAG In order to propose and vote on Serverwide Association of Gamer (SWAG) resolutions, a player must be considered &amp;ldquo;active&amp;rdquo;. Active is defined as being online within 30 days from the proposition of a resolution. If a player is not active, they may not vote on or propose resolutions until they are active.
Votes within SWAG Once a resolution is proposed, players will have 72 hours to cast their vote.</description></item></channel></rss>